{
    "translations": {
      "en": {
        "qa": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is transition from start state $\\{q0, q1, q2\\}$ with the alphabet a. Select the appropriate state:",
          "description": "Let's begin with the start state. Closure($q0$) in $M_N$ is $\\{q0,q1,q2\\}$. So this is the start state.",
          "answer": "q3, q4",
          "choices": ["q0, q1, q2", "q3, q4","q3" ,"q4"]
        },
        "qb":{
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"[T/F] Transition from start state $\\{q0, q1, q2\\}$ with the alphabet b exists?",
          "description": "Now, we should determine the the possible transitions from our new start state. To do so, we need to check the transitions from $\\{q0,q1,q2\\}$ with $a$ and $b$ ",
          "answer": "False",
          "choices": ["True", "False"]
        },
        "qc": {
          "type": "select",
          "question":"What is transition from state $\\{q3\\}$ with the alphabet b. Select the appropriate state",
          "description": "For every new node we find, we need to determine the possible transitions with $a$ and $b$. Note that, as there is a $\\lambda$ transition from $q5$ to $q1$, we will mention $q1$ whenever we use $q5$",
          "answer": ["q5", "q1"],
          "choices": ["q3","q5", "q1", "q0", "q6"]
        },
        "q0": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is transition from state $\\{$q3$, $q4$\\}$ with the alphabet a. Select the appropriate state:",
          "description": "Consider the trasition of the alphabet with node itself ",
          "answer": "q4",
          "choices": ["q0, q1, q2", "q1, q2, q3","q1, q5, q6" ,"q4"]
        },
        "q1": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is the transition from state $\\{q3, q4\\}$ with the alphabet b. Select the appropriate state:",
          "description": "Transition state nodes are highlighted nodes, becareful with what alphabet you are transitioning to",
          "answer": "q1, q5, q6",
          "choices": ["q0, q1, q2", "q1, q2, q3","q1, q5, q6" ,"q4"]
        },
        "q2": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is transition from state $\\{q1, q5, q6\\}$ with the alphabet a. Select the appropriate state:",
          "description": "Transition state nodes are highlighted nodes, becareful with what alphabet you are transitioning to",
          "answer": "q3",
          "choices": ["q0, q1, q2", "q1, q2, q3","q3, q4, q5" ,"q3"]
        },
        "q3": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is the transition from state $\\{q1, q5, q6\\}$ with the alphabet b. Select the appropriate state:",
          "description": "Transition state nodes are highlighted nodes, becareful with what alphabet you are transitioning to",
          "answer": "No Transition",
          "choices": ["q0, q1, q2", "q1, q2, q3","q1, q5, q6" ,"No Transition"]
        },
        "q4": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is the transition from state $\\{q3\\}$ with the alphabet a?",
          "description": "Transition state nodes are highlighted nodes, becareful with what alphabet you are transitioning to",
          "answer": "No Transition",
          "choices": ["q4", "q1, q2, q3","q1, q5" ,"No Transition"]
        },
        "q5": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is the trnsition from state $\\{q3\\}$ with the alphabet b?",
          "description": "Transition state nodes are highlighted nodes, becareful with what alphabet you are transitioning to",
          "answer": "q5, q1",
          "choices": ["q6","q5, q1", "q1, q5, q6","No transition"]
        },
        "q6": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is the transition from state $\\{q4\\}$ with the alphabet a?",
          "description": "Transition state nodes are highlighted nodes, becareful with what alphabet you are transitioning to",
          "answer": "q6",
          "choices": ["q6", "q1, q2, q3","q5, q1" ,"No Transition"]
        },
        "q7": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is the trnsition from state $\\{q4\\}$ with the alphabet b?",
          "description": "Transition state nodes are highlighted nodes, becareful with what alphabet you are transitioning to to",
          "answer": "No transition",
          "choices": ["q6","q5, q1", "q1, q5, q6","No transition"]
        },
        "q8": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is the transition from state $\\{q5, q1\\}$ with the alphabet a?",
          "description": "Transition state nodes are highlighted nodes, becareful with what alphabet you are transitioning to to to",
          "answer": "q3",
          "choices": ["q3", "q1, q2, q3","q5, q1" ,"No transition"]
        },
        "q9": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is the trnsition from state $\\{q5, q1\\}$ with the alphabet b?",
          "description": "Transition state nodes are highlighted nodes, becareful with what alphabet you are transitioning to to to",
          "answer": "No transition",
          "choices": ["q3","q5, q1", "q1, q5, q6","No transition"]
        },
        "q10": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is the transition from state $\\{q6\\}$ with the alphabet a?",
          "description": "Transition state nodes are highlighted nodes, becareful with what alphabet you are transitioning to to to",
          "answer": "No transition",
          "choices": ["q6", "q1, q2, q3","q5, q1" ,"No transition"]
        },
        "q11": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is the transition from state $\\{q6\\}$ with the alphabet b?",
          "description": "Transition state nodes are highlighted nodes, becareful with what alphabet you are transitioning to to to",
          "answer": "No transition",
          "choices": ["q3","q5, q1", "q1, q5, q6","No transition"]
        },
        "q12notUSed": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "src": "../../../AV/FLA/billyu/ui/FAFixer.html",
          "question":"What is the final state?",
          "answer": "q1, q2, q3",
          "choices": ["q0, q1, q2", "q1, q5, q6","q4" ]
        },
        "q13": {
          "type": "select",
          "question":"What are the final state? Note that, any state that include states $q5$ or $q6$ should be a final state",
          "answer": ["q5, q1", "q1, q5, q6", "q6"],
          "choices": ["q0, q1, q2", "q3, q4","q4", "q1, q5, q6", "q3", "q6", "q5, q1"]
        }
      }
    }
  }
  